易考范文二十六
In the above picture, when the family
step into their new apartment,
they are shocked to see big holes
in the walls and ceiling, from which their neighbors,
who are fitting up their rooms,
apologize with beaming smile for having broken the walls.
A bit exaggerating though the picture is,
it undoubtedly aims to punctuate
the importance of morality.
It is true that in recent decades,
our nation has undergone great developments
in terms of economy, but meanwhile,
some people lack the awareness of moral values.
There is prevailing selfishness in the society,
where some people gain their happiness
at the cost of others' pain or turn a blind eye
to the misfortunes of the needy.
In contrast with the material wealth
we have been possessed of, the spiritual world
in which we dwell is like a wasteland,
void of direction and love.
By no means will a nation without ethnical standards
become really influential in the world,
and the value of morality must be emphasized
in the process of building a well-off society.
Additionally, only when we have a strong sense
of social responsibility,
remain united and help each other,
can we construct a harmonious society.